Fool! Shut the radio!
We are playing cards
and not cricket!
Brother Arjun! Distribute
the cards properly!
Okay!
Where is this number 6?
lt deceived me 6 times!
Number 6 is not loyal to everybody!
Why do you see your cards?
Why don`t you play blank?
Brother Arjun! l am not
courageous like you!
You even laugh when you lose!
Hey pal! A girl without figure and
a gambler without guts! Got it?
You bring 5000 rupees. And you
dream of winning 50,000! Huh?
Bring more money!
Because money attracts money! Right?
Absolutely! Arjun!
l can see how much money..
..your money is attracting!
Today your money is
only on one track.
You are only losing it!
Wait! Things will change.
Then l will win!
No! There will be a hurdle!
- A big one!
Brother Arjun! What do you say?
Only we both are left here!
Do l have to say that too?
l am packed! 26!
l play 40!
40! Stop it, Arjun!
l play 80!
60!
20!
l am fully packed!
Brother Arjun! No cards! Give money!
Fine!
Brother Usman!
Don`t you trust me? l swear!
Arjun! What madness is this?
We are winning! We will
pack up and leave!
Show!
What do you say, brother Arjun?
What is this?
How you play!
You are gone!
Someday, l too will
become lucky, Vishal!
Someday, heaven will lie at my feet.
Someday, l too will rule the world.
No, no! We will have to walk
when the meter hits 30!
We don`t have a penny in our
pocket! Not a single one!
And you are weaving so many dreams!
Very good! Very good!
You should dream when
your pocket is empty!
You can fulfil those dreams..
..only when you have
the money, my friend!
Right, uncle?! Yes.
You lost your money! And also
the money you had borrowed!
How much? 1 lakh! Very good!
And look! Look!
There isn`t a worry line on
his face! Not one line!
He was easily winning
60,000-70,000 rupees!
But you are so great! Really great!
Once you start playing,
you don`t stop!
You become another man!
Right! The fear of losing
and the hope of winning!
The moment of tension between
these two.. it`s great!
But you won`t understand!
No, no, no! Me! How
can l understand?
l am insensible! But l
understand one thing!
lf you go on losing like this then..
Why are you harping about the loss?
Only the one who fails wins!
Do you understand that?
And today l had two winner cards!
But the queen didn`t support me!
You see, there is no
queen in my life.
So l don`t get it in cards too.
The day she comes in my
life.. then watch..
..how my luck changes.
You people too should understand!
But.. but 10 rupees per piece!
lt`s a great price! Really! lt
has just arrived from China!
And you too won`t realise which..
..is the original and which is
the duplicate! Right? - Yes!
Vishal, the specs are duplicate!
What if somebody finds out?
My shop has a reputation!
lf you say, l will get
your duplicate too!
lf you can tell me the difference..
..l will change my name!
You will change your name, Arjun!
But what about me?
Once you lose reputation
in business..
..then you lose everything..
Brother Raju, rich people who
visit malls, they themselves..
..don`t know which one is original..
..and which one is the duplicate
l am there! l give the guarantee!
lt`s a fresh piece!
Right, Arjun! Arjun!
- Yes!
Look, the price is perfect! Just
have a look at the piece!
l am giving you the guarantee!
Tell him, man.
- Yes, yes.
You just look at the samples,
brother Raju!
You like the ring?
Yes.
Hey!
What`s your name? Name!
l am asking you! You! Name!
Your name! What`s your name!
Zoya!
Nice name!
ls it a girl?
You.. did all this
to impress a girl?
Fantastic! Shinde!
He is Kedarnath Dixit`s son!
During college days, l used to
borrow books from his father.
Now too a 55 year old man
works in a book shop.
He takes out rallies
and processions.
And his son to impress a girl..
Tell me something.
My wife too wants gold bangles.
So should l too break
things like you?
Sir, how can you do it?
You are a policeman.
And she is your wife. Here, it`s
about my girlfriend, sir.
l mean my future girlfriend.
Sir, love at first sight.
lt`s something like that.
Fantastic! Shinde, he met the
girl for the first time..
..and he broke the glass!
What all will you break
once you have an affair?
Sir, whatever l do, l will
do it respectfully.
Look, l am not arresting you.
Because of your father.
l had to arrest a man
like him many times.
lt still lies heavy
on my conscience. Go.
Thank you, sir.
And listen!
Don`t take undue advantage
of your father`s decency.
Utilise your energies
in the right direction.
lt`s not a warning. lt`s an advice.
Thank you, sir!
- Go! Shinde!
That girl made a nice
entry in your life.
As soon as she came, you
went in the lockup!
What? Now what are you thinking?
About that queen!
- What!
Yes!
l can`t forget her face!
The way she was looking
at the ring..
..the sorrow on her face on
not being able to buy it..
..l can`t forget it.
That sorrow seemed like a
blotch on her pretty face.
l want to erase that blotch of
sorrow from that pretty face.
Sorrow? Pretty face? Blotch?
What nonsense!
Brother Usman, you and here? How
are you? ls everything fine?
l am fine, Arjun! But
brother has called you.
Brother? Brother Patel? Where?
There! ln the car!
Yes, come on! Let`s go!
You were dreaming. Now count
the stars, in daylight!
How are you, brother?
How are you? Fine?
l was going somewhere.
l thought l will take
you both along too.
Come, sit in the car.
Where are we going, brother?
Khandala.
We will eat, drink and have
fun. What else? Come.
Brother, why Khandala?
Khandala, no? Then.. l will
show you a trailer!
Who are you? How did you come in?..
Where is he?
- What are you doing?
Where is he? Where have
you hidden him?
He is not at home!
Where is he? Where is he?
Here he is! The old
man is hiding here!
You will not repay Patel`s money!
Taking Patel`s money.. you
don`t repay it! Move!
What are you doing?
- l said move!
Leave him!
Will you kill him? Leave
him! l beg you!
Just watch his plight now!
Move! Move!
Please!
Leave him!
Somebody save him!
Listen to me carefully!
lf l don`t get money
by tomorrow evening..
..then each part of your body
will disappear daily!
Got it?
- l will repay it!
lt was a nice trailer, brother!
Full of action!
l understood the film!
l understood that if l don`t
repay the money on time..
..then one by one you will
export my body parts too!
l won`t like it. But
l will have to do it.
You should do it! You
don`t give charity!
lt`s your business.
And whoever mixes business
and friendship..
..loses his business.
You have to use foul means.
lt`s right!
Brother, but you don`t
worry about your money.
l don`t take tension. l give it.
No, you do it. Your way of
giving tension is great!
l will give it to you too!
Money! Money!
ln a day or two!
Yes, brother! He will
give it to you!
Brother, l will give
it to you for sure!
Arjun, this is the deposit money.
l want the double of it!
Double for sure! Okay? Okay?
Yes, let go of my collar!
Uncle Gaffur! Come on!
Where?
Where l go everyday!
l am craving to play
cards and earn money.
Arjun!
- Yes!
This is the last over. lndia
needs just 3 runs to win.
Let`s watch this over
and then leave.
Uncle, why do you want
to see lndia losing?
What are you saying?
Sehwag is going to play this over.
ls that so?
He will get out on the next ball.
ls that so? Are you an astrologer..
..that you know everything?
Sixth sense, uncle Gaffur! My
intuition. lt`s always right.
You are wrong. He won`t be out.
lndia will win this match.
Hey!
Let`s go!
Arjun, your intuition came true.
We lost the match.
By the way.. you are wasting
your time in playing cards.
lf your intuition is so accurate
then why don`t you bet?
Bet on matches.
God willing you will earn lakhs!
Uncle! Follow that sumo!
- But..
Follow it! My queen is in it.
- But the signal is red, Arjun.
Come on! Quickly!
Uncle, overtake it!
- l am doing it!
Left turn!
- l am taking it!
Drive fast!
- ls it a plane?
Who is she, Arjun, for whom
we are breaking signals?
Bye!
- Bye!
Hey!
Wait! Wait! Where are you going?
Thank you, sir!
Zoya!
He is the same man!
- Who? - Zoya!
The one who was in the
shopping mall today..
But why has he come up like
a Spiderman? - Zoya!
Because he is like this!
Spiderman! What?
Hi! Give me your hand!
What?
Look, l will fall and die!
Please give me your hand!
l want to come inside!
Thank you!
Hang on!
How did you find my address?
People who search even find God.
This was that ring, right?
You have bought it?
Yes. Shall l show you the bill?
Why did you buy it?
- Because you liked it!
Oh! l like that building.
Will you buy it?
Yes. l will try.
Why?
ls your surname Tata, Mallya,
Birla or something like that?
No. Dixit.
Besides my name you don`t know
anything about me. Still..
ln two meetings l found
your name and address.
ln future meetings l
will know you too.
Future meetings?
- Yes.
Won`t you meet me again after..
..getting such an expensive gift?
Do you know what giving
a ring to a girl means?
Look, you ask so many questions.
Please take the ring.
- What if l don`t take it?
What can l do? This ring will
get what it`s destined for.
Either your finger or that dustbin.
Are you mad?
You really threw it.
Wear it a bit.
A bit? How can l wear it a bit?
l will have to wear it fully.
lt looks more beautiful.
Now keep this with you.
When l feel l should take it from
you, l will take it. Now go.
ls there no door in your house?
Why? Go back the way you came in.
lf l want to meet you again, will
l have to hang and call you?
Why? People who search
even find God.
So they can find the
number too. Right?
He disconnected Patel`s call.
Even after showing him the trailer,
he dared to do this.
From today start beating him.
- Okay, brother.
Hi. This is Zoya from Spike.
We sell you the world.
How can l help you?
God has given me the
right number. Hi.
You?
- You forgot my name so soon?
Arjun!
- What is he saying?
You are forgetting that
right now l am working.
And if you want to talk to me then..
..you will have to buy something.
Because nothing is free in life.
So what will you buy today?
Happiness.
Happiness? Then you have
dialled the wrong number.
Maybe you don`t know that..
..you can`t buy happiness
with money.
People who say this, don`t know..
..where to shop for happiness.
What will l have to buy?
l have so much that you
will get tired of buying.
Wrong. You will get
tired of selling it.
ls that so? Tell me!
What?
What`s wrong with him?
32518910!
- Okay! Okay! That`s it! That`s it!
Listen, l have met
my monthly target.
But l have still not
achieved my target.
What do you mean?
The target of meeting you.
l can meet you only after my shift.
lt means l will have to wait
outside your office till morning?
What?
l wish that day instead
of you l had seen..
..that ring from outside
the showcase.
l don`t believe this guy!
Hi!
- Hi!
For you limits, boundaries..
..these words mean nothing, right?
The man who stays within limits..
..can`t achieve anything in life.
And all the things which
you have bought..
..how will you pay for it?
The way the whole world pays.
Swipe the credit card and enjoy.
Okay! Credit card! But you will
have to pay to the bank.
Yes, in 55 days.
And in 55 days l will
find out 555 ways.
And if you don`t find any way then?
The whole world lives on hope.
lt includes you and me too. Let`s
have coffee in a 5 star.
Coffee? ln a 5 star?
- Yes.
You can`t use credit cards
at the tea stalls.
Zoya!
- l don`t know what..
Zoya! Coffee in a 5 star!
Arjun, those who don`t have
their own vehicle..
..they have to use the
call centre`s vehicle!
What kind of rule is this?
- lt`s a rule!
Oh God! He is mad!
lt means l will have to buy a car!
How is that?
You want a car!
Yes!
He wants a car!
Buy it! Buy it right now! l will
get it for you right now!
Brother Usman, you?
Arjun! Brother Patel has said that..
..if you don`t repay
his money today..
Money?
- Then he will take off your pants!
We had repaid the money.
What did you say? What did you say?
What did you say?
He will take off my pants!
You should have told
me before that..
..he needs my pants
and not money. Here.
Arjun! Arjun, why are you
taking off your pants?
Take it! Take it!
Arjun! Arjun!
- Wait!
Arjun!
- What did you say?
Brother, look. He is joking.
He is taking his pants off.
Brother, you? Greetings,
brother. How are you?
Brother, l gave him money
to give you. 1 lakh.
But if he didn`t give it to you
then what can l do, brother?
Take him aside.
- Brother, l will..
Brother!
- Arjun! What joke is this?
l gave him for sure!
Brother, why are you getting angry?
Come! Have breakfast!
Something cold! Come! Come!
Come on! Come on!
l want my money, today,
right now! And here!
Brother, can`t l get
a day or two? A bit.
Brother, don`t listen to him.
l myself gave him money.
l told him to give you the money.
Sir, please let me go.
Sir, forgive me.
Please, sir. l don`t
even know him, sir.
l know him just for
the past one month.
Brother, you want your money..
here and right now.
Right?
- How many times should l say it?
No, l am confirming.
And if l don`t give it to you, you
will kill me. l am going to die.
And the last wish of
the dying man.. .
..is fulfilled all over the world.
And it`s obvious that you will
fulfil my last wish. Correct?
So brother, my last wish
is that before dying..
..l want to bet on this match.
And that too with your money.
- What?
You don`t have to give money.
You just have to say that
you are giving the money.
Arjun!
- You think l am a fool!
He is a fool! l am telling you..
Brother, l am not afraid of
dying. You can kill me.
But what will you get? Nothing.
But if you help me..
then you will get..
..4 lakhs instead of 1 lakh.
4.. 4..
He is mad! He doesn`t know anything!
l am telling you! You
won`t get anything!
You come with me! You will be
ruined! l am telling you!
You come..
- Sit!
Tell me something, Arjun!
- Yes!
lf you bet with my money then..
..what`s the guarantee
that you will win?
Brother, a few years ago an
English movie was released.
Sixth Sense. You must have seen it.
l can`t understand Hindi movies.
How will l understand
English movies?
That`s it! That`s it!
For the first time, l am going to
put my life at stake and bet.
My sixth sense can`t deceive me.
Shall we go?
Okay!
4 lakhs! From where will
we bring 4 lakhs?
We can`t even repay 1 lakh!
Brother Patel, you?
You have come to bet?
He will bet on my behalf.
So what`s the price?
England favourite 8-10.
How much for wicket and 6?
For wicket, 1 for 10
and for 6, 1 for 3.
1000 rupees!
That`s it? Give me a bundle!
Brother, don`t listen
to him. 1 lakh..
lt`s 5. Arjun, listen.
What are you doing? Leave it.
1000 rupees. On Dada.
Now he will hit a 6.
lt`s a 6!
Fluke.
3000. Sehwag out.
6 lakhs!
Your 4 lakhs!
Arjun won 6 lakhs!
l told you, sir! He will..
Your deposit money.
- Thanks.
l know him since a long time.
Since many years.
He is my friend. Come on. Let`s go.
Not yet. l have just repaid the
debt. l have to buy a car too.
Because without a
car you can`t love.
No car. No love.
Brother Raju, what`s the rate
of winning and losing?
England 23-25.
23-25!
Arjun, let`s go! Arjun, we
have won enough! Let`s go!
40 on England!
Arjun! What are you saying?
On England! You mean lndia will win!
Brother Patel, from where
have you brought him?
He will ruin you.
lndia will win! lndia
is already losing.
Brother, tell him to
do what l am saying.
No, brother! No! Don`t
listen to him!
l am saying that lndia will win!
- Brother..
l will give you 20 lakhs! 20 lakhs!
Do as the guy says.
Okay, brother. lf you want
to lose, then fine.
Brother!
lndia has won, brother!
Give me some place in your heart.
Make me yours a bit.
Dream about me a bit.
Cherish me in your memories a bit.
l love you a lot, beloved.
l am deeply, madly in love
with you, beloved.
Give me some place in your heart.
Make me yours a bit.
Dream about me a bit.
Cherish me in your memories a bit.
Brother Raju!
You have come again?
To bet on this game!
Yes!
Again l lost!
You bet so well. Why don`t
you become a bookie?
l will bring this world
at your feet.
My love is crazy.
Nobody loves you as much as l do.
You are my worship.
l love you a lot, beloved.
l am deeply, madly in love
with you, beloved.
Give me some place in your heart.
Make me yours a bit.
Dream about me a bit.
Cherish me in your memories a bit.
Say what lies in your heart.
Your desire.
Keep no secrets from me.
Trust me.
l love you a lot, beloved.
l am deeply, madly in love
with you, beloved.
TV in the kitchen! TV in
the bedroom! What luxury!
What else do you have?
So many soaps.
Never even heard the name.
l know the name of just
one soap. Hamam.
Remember? Until the soap wouldn`t
finish completely..
..your mother would not
take out the new one.
You remember it, don`t you?
But here it feels
that for everyday..
..in fact for every hour
there is a new soap.
Arjun, after seeing your
home l understood..
..that in a shanty we don`t
have things we need because..
..in these houses there are
more things than you need.
Dad, please. At least today..
Fine! Fine! Let`s have lunch.
Zoya! There is a huge difference..
..between the father and
the son`s thinking!
Since childhood he is like this.
When his mother used to cook..
..the clanking of her bangles
would make me so happy..
..that l can`t express it.
But he liked the clanking of coins.
l would say that a person should..
..dream within his limits.
But he would say that first
you should dream..
..and then think about your stature.
l would say that a man should
control his desires..
..because desires are limitless.
But he would say that the
one who kills his desires..
..is as good as dead though alive.
And today, look. My
son has everything.
Dad, are you praising
me or taunting me?
Why do you always think
that l taunt you?
Tell me something.
What work do you do that
in such little time..
..you have earned so much?
Sports business.
Sports?
l deal in the import-export
of cricket gear.
Sports gloves, bats! Such things.
Nice business.
l just knew that in a short time you
can`t earn a lot using fair means.
But look, the world
has changed. Good.
Very good!
Dad, you are not eating anything.
l am done.
An ordinary man like me can`t eat
much of a 5 star hotel`s food.
lf l get a nice betel leaf
then it will be great!
Yes. l will just get it.
l will just come.
l will get coffee.
Zoya. Arjun lies a lot.
What?
Yes. He proudly looks in the
other person`s eyes and lies!
Because of his lies, his mother
and l`ve endured many troubles.
Now it`s your turn.
We couldn`t change him. Maybe
you can do something.
A woman can set a
limit if she wants.
He shouldn`t go so far away that..
Arjun!
When l was 15 years old..
my parents got divorced.
They both got married again
and got busy in their lives.
No. Hear me out, Arjun.
l lived with mom.
l came to Mumbai with the
dream to be a dancer.
l didn`t get much work so l started
working in a call centre.
Whenever l get the chance, l
danced at other`s weddings.
For extra income.
This is my truth, Arjun. And yours?
What do you mean?
Arjun, the business which
you do.. l mean..
l understood. My father told
you something, right?
Arjun! Arjun!
He has told you for sure! He
must have said that l lie!
He must have said that..
Zoya, he is jealous of me!
He is jealous of my
success and fame!
This is not so, Arjun!
- Yes, it is!
He couldn`t achieve
anything in life!
And he talks of principles,
values and honesty.
Arjun, but..
The truth is that he
hides his failure..
..and his poverty using these words!
What he doesn`t have,
that is bad and wrong!
That`s why he doesn`t
like anything l do!
l am earning money. lt`s bad.
l am not living with him in
his small shanty. lt`s bad.
Arjun, you are mistaken.
And you too believed him?
- Arjun, l was just..
You too think l am wrong?
l am wrong?
Arjun, l..
- Forget it!
And henceforth please don`t
ask me these things!
Don`t ask any question and
don`t hear any lies!
lt`s a saying!
Something like this..
Listen, l am sorry. Zoya..
l run my own business.
Earlier too l did it.
But you were not there
so l was not lucky.
Now you are with me. Okay?
l believe you, Arjun. l am with
you because l trust you.
But don`t ever let my
trust break, Arjun.
Because the day this trust breaks..
..that day our relationship
too will break.
l won`t break it.
Forget your trust.. l won`t
even break a signal.
l love you.
- Love you, too.
Sachin 95!
Zaheer, 3 wickets.
Less than 50 runs.
42-45.
20 on 48.
10 on Sameer.
Okay.
Tell me.
Police.
- Good shot!
After closing down beer bars,
they have nothing else to do.
How much time?
15 minutes.
Clear the setup.
Sir! Will you take something?
Tea, coffee, biscuit?
- Stop the music!
Look outside! Search the place!
Fantastic! Fun with girls
in a 5 star hotel.
Sir, the stars on your uniform
too must`ve increased.
So it`s my duty to increase
my stature too.
Sir, l was giving a small
party for my friends.
Okay. Time`s up. Party is over. Out.
Check out.
Yes sir. - l hope you had
a good evening. Thanks.
Come on!
Okay.. l too will leave.
Wait!
Who is he?
Sir, it`s a party for my friends.
Who else will he be besides
being my friend?
Yes, sir. l am his friend.
He is my friend.
Was betting going on here on..
..the lndia-Sri Lanka cricket match?
No, sir!
l am thinking of betting.
My wife is asking for gold bangles.
You must be knowing.. what`s
the current rate? Right?
No, sir.
Sir, you are talking about rates.
l don`t even know the names of the
players in our cricket team.
Yes, sir. He doesn`t
know anything. He..
Why is your friend sweating?
Sir, it`s his ailment.
To sweat in AC.
l told him to show to a doctor.
But he doesn`t listen to me. Today,
get a check up done.
Yes! Sir, l feel cold
in heat. lt`s reverse.
lt`s pretty funny.
Found nothing, sir.
Fantastic! l`m leaving you all
due to lack of evidence.
The next time l meet you, it`ll
be straight to prison.
Sir, seriously you are mistaken.
You take me seriously.
This path of crime looks
enthralling from afar.
lf not for your father
then think about her..
..for whom you broke the
showroom glass that day.
What will she go through when..
..she sees you handcuffed?
Change your path.
Sir, shall l tell you something?
Bet on Sri Lanka. Sister-in-law
will get her bangles.
My heart said. So l said it.
You had put us into trouble.
lf you are so scared of cops..
..then go and sell books
with my father.
Yes, l think l will have to do that.
Arjun, listen to me.
Our old business was fine.
We`re flying too high.
That inspector was right.
lf we are arrested
then what about me?
l don`t have a family. But
what about you? And Zoya?
What will she think?
What will she think? She will
think if she finds out.
You are a coward.
Vishal, l have been
born to fly high.
l want to hold the entire
sky in my fist.
This is just the beginning.
Just watch where l land up.
Now set up everything.
10 overs must be over.
Are you Arjun Dixit?
Yes.
- Let`s go.
Greetings, boss. He has come.
Sorry l had to bring
you here like this.
Was it a trouble?
l wanted to see how that man looks..
..who has shut down my
top bookies` business.
l`ve also heard that
you come to know..
..what will happen in the match.
l try. And my calculation
turns out to be accurate.
So tell me. What will happen
in today`s match?
The bowling team will win.
What?
80 runs will be made in 6 overs.
Meaning around 280.
The other team will easily
make this score.
For the bowlers there is
nothing on this pitch.
And their 4 batsmen
are in a good form.
lf their captain wants, he
can alone score this much.
The one who bets on the other team..
..is the biggest fool in the world.
So l am that fool.
l have betted on the team
which is batting.
How can you be so sure it will lose?
Calculation! Confidence!
lt means l will lose
crores in this match.
lf you want, the team on which
you`ve betted can win.
How?
Cricketers are Gods for their fans..
..but they are human beings.
The wife of this team`s captain
likes diamond rings.
And he likes expensive watches.
Congrats, captain. Today, your
players are playing well.
Who are you?
l`m talking to you in
the locker room..
..so l must be somebody.
So listen to me carefully.
There isn`t much difference
between..
..cricketers and prostitutes.
Both lose their life
as their youth ends.
And you know the plight of
ex-cricketers very well, sir.
Somebody is committing suicide..
..and somebody is drunk
and getting nostalgic.
Those who can talk, blabber
on news channels.
And those who can laugh, laugh
without any reason..
..in some laughter show.
And you neither know how
to talk nor how to laugh.
And sir l always say, make
money too, not just runs.
Sir.. 50 lakhs for you
and 25 lakhs each..
..for two middle order batsmen.
Sir, lose in this match.
l will leave now.
And yes, sir! l`ve kept a few
Rolex watches in your room.
You will like it. Goodbye.
Brother, tell your bookies to raise
the rate as much as they can.
Have you thought well?
The man who thinks, only keeps
thinking all his life.
The home team are in pursuit
of 286 runs for victory.
lncrease the rate.
Totally, what you like,
it`s gone for a 4.
The captain..
He is getting close to 50.
And the visitors are 78 for no loss.
Brother, he is the captain.
He can`t be out so soon.
The run rate is up
to the mark of 5.8.
He is out. They have got
their first wicket.
The home team is all charged up.
Another wicket. The batsman
tried to whack that for a 4.
Who is going to win this final?
What a great match we
are watching here!
Straight off the middle of the bat.
We are down to the last over.
They need a run a ball.
The home team is 280 for 9.
6 runs and 5 balls.
And that was close.
He could have been out.
What a great match we
are watching here!
6 to win just from 4 balls.
Just 2 runs from the
last three balls.
Everybody here is fighting it out!
What a match we have got here!
He has bowled him! l just
can`t believe it!
This is why this is the most..
..incredible match
you have ever seen.
The team has done it.
They have won the championship.
And the crowd is on their feet!
He played wonderfully well.
You`re neither greedy to win..
..nor afraid to lose.
You will prosper a lot.
You will benefit others.
But remember one thing.
ln our business people can enter..
..but they can`t exit.
Now you`ll not bet.
You`ll set things up.
Either here in South
Africa or in lndia.
You have to decide.
lndia is fine for dreaming.
And it`s the world of globalisation.
l want to make my heaven here.
How did you manage all this, Arjun?
A big company`s senior officer
will live in a big house.
Here.
Listen!
My heart says.
Greed is intoxicating.
Look.
Whose prayer is it?
The one who touches the sky,
he is the lucky one.
Everyday, life is new.
Give me such a beautiful
punishment.
Heaven is here.
Listen!
Why worry about the world?
l did what l wanted.
Look!
What magic this is!
l have turned stone into gold.
Everyday, life is new.
Give me such a beautiful
punishment.
Heaven is here.
Money is needed to live.
Money is the lesson of death.
The magic of money is great.
Everyday, life is new.
Give me such a beautiful
punishment.
Heaven is here.
Listen!
What is in the eyes?
My heart got whatever it wanted.
Greetings, ACP Shekhar
Malhotra from CBl.
l have been called from lndia.
Can l come in?
Come in.
- Thank you.
Fantastic! lt`s like money
dripping from everything.
Hey, nice view.
Amazing!
A window breaker..
..has built a palace of
mirrors for himself!
Do you know Arjun?
Do you really don`t
know anything or..
..are you pretending to be ignorant.
What do you want to say?
Something that.. you wouldn`t
want to hear.
What do you think, Arjun has got
his hands on the lamp of..
Arjun has a business,
of import-export.
lmport-export!
Yes, he does do import-export.
But of arms, ammunitions, RDX.
He works for the underworld.
Underworld don Abu Abraham.
Arjun is his special fixer.
From the money Arjun
earns, he funds..
..international smuggling
and terrorism.
And what terrorists do
all over the world..
..l don`t think l need
to tell you that.
lf you don`t believe me, you
can see these photographs.
And Zoya, the police
here believe that..
..Arjun is involved in every
activity as much as Abu is.
Zoya, what`s wrong?
What is all this?
l can`t wear it.
These clothes. This jewellery.
All of them are stained with blood.
What?
Yes.
On your money and..
..everything that you
bought with this money.
Blood!
Have you gone crazy?
You won`t see it, Arjun.
Because money has made you blind.
You can only see money.
You have a business
of import-export.
Papa was right that you..
But l..
How could l ever believe you?
Don`t ask a question and
don`t listen to a lie!
That`s what you said, isn`t it?
Zoya, who had come here?
ACP Malhotra.
He has reached here too to
narrate his false story.
False story!
ls this a lie?
ls all of this a lie?
Yes, it`s all a lie!
l can make a photo of yours
along with George Bush!
Does that mean you work for him?
Zoya, all this is a conspiracy
against me.
They are trying to trap me.
The police need someone they
can put the entire blame on.
And who can be an easier
target than me?
Because l am successful.
No lndian has achieved
so much success..
..in such a short time like l did!
That`s why!
l have been toiling day and
night and earning money..
..for you! For you!
ACP Malhotra just told
you once! Just once!
And you believed him!
You believed everything he said.
You know what?
l don`t need this.
l am going.
Arjun!
Arjun, don`t go.
Arjun, please.
Arjun, listen to me they will..
Zoya, if Shekhar has said
it then it`s the truth.
He is an honest officer.
lt`s Arjun`s habit of hiding the
truth by creating a scene.
This turn had to come in his path.
The only regret is that at this
turn you are all alone..
..and that too in foreign land.
But there is always a time
in everyone`s life..
..to take a difficult decision.
While taking any decision,
don`t fall weak.
Many a times you have
to be bad for someone..
..for their betterment.
Only you can save him.
And if you feel you can`t,
then get out of his life.
lt`s not intelligent to drown
with a drowning man.
Why will you suffer for
something that he did?
Zoya, can you understand
what l am telling you?
Yes.
Yes, Vishal.
Zoya, please don`t disconnect
the phone, listen to me.
Zoya, l don`t know what
had happened to me.
Please forgive me.
Zoya, l want to meet you.
l want to tell you something
important.
l wanted to say it for
quite some time..
..but l couldn`t say it.
You are listening, aren`t you?
Zoya, you will meet me, won`t you?
Okay.
Okay. l love you.
l had told you, right?
One day Zoya will find
out everything.
What if she doesn`t agree?
What will you do?
Vishal, l can`t even think
about living without Zoya.
l won`t let her go away from me.
She will calm down by
tomorrow morning.
Then l will appease her.
l will do whatever it takes.
Hi!
How am l looking?
You are still not in a good mood.
No, l am fine.
Good.
Then let`s get married.
How long will l carry
this ring in my pocket?
lf someone picks my pocket,
then that will be bad.
We can have a tiff after
the marriage, okay?
Arjun, first you will have to
tell me the entire truth.
ln every relation there
is a moment Arjun..
..when it is very important
for the truth to be revealed.
l should know what my
future husband does.
You are right.
Yes Zoya, it`s true that l don`t
have an import-export..
..but a match-fixing business.
l fix cricket matches.
And l do it because
l am very good at it.
And l don`t think l am doing
anything bad or wrong.
Betting is legal here..
..and l think match-fixing
should be made legal too.
And the activities of Abu Abraham..
..should be made legal too.
Zoya, l only fix matches
for Abu Abraham.
Because only he has the
network around the world.
l don`t have anything to do
with his other business.
And do you know what he does
with the match-fixing money?
He makes arms, bombs, kills people.
Zoya, the tax money that
we pay the government..
..is also used to buy
bombs and cannons.
So?
lt doesn`t make any difference
to you Arjun that..
Yes, it doesn`t make any difference.
lt doesn`t make any
difference to me..
..what Abu Abraham does with
the match-fixing money.
lf he buys guns, cannons,
that`s his problem.
People are dying in the world,
that`s their problem.
All l know is that l work for him..
..and l am paid handsomely
for it, that`s it.
For God`s sake, Arjun.
Zoya, God, Lord.. doesn`t
do anything.
You have to do everything
on your own.
And l am doing what l should!
And l will keep doing it.
Why did you do that, Zoya?
Thank you, Zoya.
l can understand what you must
be going through right now.
Why did you call me here?
Zoya, Abu`s men must be looking
for you everywhere.
lt`s not safe here.
l can`t even protect you.
That`s why Zoya, this is some
money and an air-ticket.
Go back to lndia.
l didn`t get Arjun arrested to
return to lndia with some money.
Anyway, you won`t understand.
Look Zoya, it will take
at least 5-6 years..
..before he is released from jail.
Till then, what will you do here?
You don`t have any work, nor
do you have a work permit.
What are you going to do here?
l don`t need your help,
l will manage.
You will need a lot of money
in such a mission.
You are fighting a war.
Don`t worry, l will arrange for it.
Goodbye.
Arrange for it!
How will l arrange for it?
Every business is down.
There is loss in every business.
Who will cover the losses?
You!
Or you!
This.
This world cup will
make money for me.
lt will bring us 50 times
the profit we have earned..
..in every business till now.
Where is Arjun?
Arjun turned out to
be very stubborn.
The police couldn`t make him
confess anything about any of us.
He will come out in 5-6 months.
5-6 months!
Till then this world
cup will be over.
Then how will we make money?
You go to Australia and
meet that lawyer..
..who had defended Ansari`s case.
Tell him, we are ready for
any amount that it takes.
l want Arjun released
as soon as possible.
Fantastic.
You must be feeling very good
after coming out, isn`t it?
No, l am feeling very bad.
l am thinking of going
back in again.
lf you won`t mend your ways..
..then you will have
to come back in.
You had me arrested using
a girl as a bait.
Don`t consider this as your victory.
l don`t change paths,
l make my own path.
Meaning.. you won`t change
your activities.
Not activities, business.
The business of showing dreams
to the common man..
..and making them real.
You think about this business too.
Because l don`t think you have
still brought bangles..
..for sister-in-law. l will
give you a great tip.
Thanks for the offer. Bite?
- No.
But you and l both know that..
..the people who have freed you..
..have done it for fixing,
not for betting.
That`s why l will
give you one offer.
Come on this side, then you
can start a new beginning.
That side will be the
beginning of the end.
Are you giving me an
offer or a warning?
Both.
l will always keep an eye on you.
Don`t you have any other
work other than..
..keeping an eye on me?
What can l do? You`ve become
such an important man.
Till the time you were in jail,
fixing was closed too.
Now that you have come out,
it will start again.
That`s why.
And because, l want to save you.
l know you.
Thanks for thinking
so much about me.
Fantastic.
Wow, your entire style has changed.
You have become completely
colourful.
Have you changed from
inside in 5 months..
..or is it the same old
stock from Dharavi?
What are you thinking?
About your girlfriend?
Who had laid a trap for you!
Afridi has a bad habit.
He always tampers with the ball..
..and always escapes easily.
Your girl, was an out-swinging
delivery for you.
You should have left it.
But you played it.
Suddenly the ball came inwards..
..and went towards your
wicket and bowled you.
l was mad.
l thought of kidnapping
the girl and..
Then l thought she
is your girlfriend.
So you explain to her.
You are right.
Stop the car.
l will meet you later.
Come on, Vishal.
Remember one more thing while going.
Think about your ball.. l mean
your girl after the world-cup.
And it will be even better if
you don`t think about her.
Because this time if this
girl bowls you over..
..then you are done for.
Vishal, where is Zoya?
Shakeel told you, first
concentrate on the work..
..then we will see.
Don`t take Shakeel`s side.
Tell me where Zoya is!
How would l know where Zoya is?
Then who knows Vishal?
He knows! He knows!
Vishal, who knows?
Why are you getting angry on me?
Since you have been arrested..
..there is no trace of her!
l haven`t tried to look for her.
And it will be better
if you don`t either.
She had only one motive
for coming in your life.
To get you arrested.
She did her work and disappeared.
lt will be better that
you do your work too.
Look. The list of the forthcoming
cricket matches.
Tell me, where do we have to fix it?
No Vishal, l have
to meet Zoya first.
l need answers to many questions.
l won`t let her go away
from my life so easily.
l will find her no matter
where she is.
Arjun!
Zoya, Arjun has been
released from jail.
Abu has freed him and he`ll
surely come to meet you.
Hello!
- Piya, this is Arjun speaking.
Hi Arjun, how are you?
ls Zoya in Mumbai!
- Zoya, no.
The boss is very angry.
Not with you, because
of your girlfriend.
He was saying that his work
is not being done..
..because of that girl.
He said use all our men
to search for her..
..and as soon as she is found..
l stopped him.
How long will l be able to stop him?
Only 4 months are left
for the world cup.
And boss` blood pressure is rising.
Why do you want to be caught
on this wide ball?
You are feeling bad, isn`t it?
l mean to say that you better
start the match fixing.
Forget about the girl, let her be.
We will bring her in front of you.
l swear on the Lord. Okay?
Now go.
That hard hitter Shahdab is
practicing in the nets.
Meet him and deal with him.
Until then l will send
my men after your girl.
l will see how she is not found.
Really, what a beautiful wicket.
l swear on Lord, l will
have real fun batting.
Arjun. How are you doing?
- Fine man.
Arjun sir, l have been hearing
a lot of praises about you.
l have heard that you recognise..
..the likes and dislikes of the
players. That`s great man.
Like l have understood your likes.
On the ground, you like
to field on the fine leg.
And out of the ground you like
to watch fine leg. - Right.
Well, there are a lot
of similarities..
..between cricket and girls.
- Oh really?!
Cricket is a.. you know, a
very unpredictable game..
..and girls are quite
unpredictable too.
You always have a problem
playing with a new ball.
And tolerating new girls too.
And.. power play is very important
for both of them.
Right?
- Yes, man.
lnteresting.
You are quite an interesting person.
l am.
And l want to make your first
match interesting too.
That is with the weakest
team of the world cup!
Actually sir, if you
win this match..
..then it won`t be any fun.
History and money will be made..
..only when you lose this match.
And.. only throwing away the
matches is not match-fixing. No.
Share with us the information
about every match.
l promise you, you will
make a lot of profits.
All the information.
l didn`t get you.
You can see only fine leg
here, isn`t it? - Yes.
Come, l will take you to a place
where fine leg is a bit deep.
You can watch the
gully and slip too.
Love lasts only for four days.
And only a long separation
after that.
Love lasts only for four days.
And only a long separation
after that.
Without you my heart is restless.
Without you my life is empty.
After a long time,
l remembered you.
l was so lost in my melody.
l even forgot your footsteps.
l have been so lonely for so long.
l have forgotten the path of love.
l was so lost in my melody.
l even forgot your footsteps.
l have been so lonely for so long.
l have forgotten the path of love.
l was entangled in life!
What can l say? What can l say?
Without you my heart is restless.
Without you my life is
empty. What`s her name?
Angel.
l want to meet her.
Only after the club shuts
down in the night.
After a long time,
l remembered you.
Lord!
Hey, what are you doing on Saturday?
l want to see that new movie.
You are in a hurry, Zoya.
Arjun.
Wow!
You recognized me.
l thought if we meet somewhere..
..you will refuse to recognize me.
Thanks, Angel.
What else did you change?
What happened? Why are
you so astonished?
What did you think, l will
spend all my life in jail..
..l will never come out?
Zoya..
l.. wanted to ask you something.
How much money did you
accept from the police?
You did all this for
money, isn`t it?
Why?
l did everything for you.
l gave you everything you desired.
Then why?
Zoya, you will have to answer.
Tell me, why?
After getting me arrested, you
are dancing in this bar.
Zoya, you will have
to answer. Tell me.
Tell me, why you did that?
Why did you do that, Zoya?
Because l love you damn it!
l love you.
That`s why.
Love doesn`t mean lying and
showering a lot of money..
..and then hurting that person!
Love means to get someone arrested..
..to give him a good life!
To suffer after he is gone!
And to wait for him!
What l was doing!
You felt very bad going
to jail, isn`t it, Arjun?
l had to face much more
than that, Arjun.
l was dancing in this club, so
that l can earn some money.
For us.
So that when you come
out of the jail..
..we can start a new life.
But the people who have
bailed you out..
..they don`t want that, Arjun.
They have defeated me today, Arjun.
l feel so helpless.
All my efforts have gone in vain.
There is nothing that l can do.
l feel so helpless.
Zoya, l am sorry.
l will change myself for you.
Now l won`t do all that l did.
Zoya, give me another chance.
Be with me.
You know, staying away from you..
..l realised the importance
of being with you.
l love you.
What l didn`t even imagine
in my dreams..
..you have showered
so much love on me.
Whenever l was under
the scorching sun..
..your tresses gave me shade.
What l didn`t even imagine
in my dreams..
..you have showered
so much love on me.
Whenever l was under
the scorching sun..
..your tresses gave me shade.
You are there. You are there.
You are in my words.
You are in my dreams, my thoughts
and my intentions.
You are there. You are there.
You are in my words.
You are in my dreams, my thoughts
and my intentions.
You are in my intentions.
l say we can fall in love.
l say l can fall in love with you.
Brother, Arjun has hidden behind
his girlfriend`s veil.
Shall l kill him?
He will come.
He will surely come.
Humans can change everything
but not their nature.
And greed is Arjun`s nature.
And as for his love story.
Then remember one thing.
When poverty knocks on the door..
..then love leaps out of the window.
Here is your pay for the month.
Thanks.
- You are welcome.
Zoya let me bet on this match.
l can turn 5,000 dollars
into 50,000 dollars.
And there is nothing bad in it.
Everyone does a bit of it.
Who is above it; who is below
it. No one sees that.
There`s no score board.
l worked sincerely
for so many days..
..but what happened, nothing!
By earning some money..
Zoya, after this bet,
l will stop this too.
You don`t understand.
l say we can fall in love.
l say l can fall in love with you.
There isn`t a single moment..
..that doesn`t include you.
Even if l fall asleep
in the nights..
..your part in me doesn`t
fall asleep.
Your part in me doesn`t
You are there. You are there.
You are in my words.
You are in my dreams, my thoughts
and my intentions.
You are there. You are there.
You are in my words.
You are in my dreams, my thoughts
and my intentions.
You are in my intentions.
l think he has gone clean.
There is no talk of cricket
or match fixing.
Fantastic.
Love is showing its colours.
lt`s a gift that l have
received from you.
This smile that`s glowing
on my face.
My face can`t even hide it.
The happiness that l have
got after finding you.
You are there. You are there.
You are in my words.
You are in my dreams, my thoughts
and my intentions.
You are there. You are there.
You are in my words.
You are in my dreams, my thoughts
and my intentions.
You are in my intentions.
Boss, you and here?
l was passing by so l thought
of meeting my special friend.
Not special, but l can
call you friend.
Boss, you shouldn`t have come here.
The police is watching
me all the time..
..and this isn`t my home too.
lt shouldn`t be too.
Look, my most talented fixer
lives in such a house..
..that`s an insult to me.
That`s why l have come here.
Boss, try to understand.
My girlfriend will be
arriving any minute.
lf she sees you here then..
Then what?
lf she creates a racket
we will kill her.
What?
l was joking.
Now l can`t work for you.
Now you are joking.
Are you lying to me or to yourself?
Come on.
Area. 150 acres.
Mahogany wood.
ltalian marble and furniture.
Space for parking 25-50 cars.
French chandelier.
lndoor-outdoor swimming pool.
Tennis court.
Private gym.
Everything that can
be found in a palace.
lt`s exactly like heaven, isn`t it?
l wanted to gift this heaven to you.
After the world cup.
l will give you this place
and so much money..
..that you can spend all
your life like a prince.
You and Zoya.. that`s the name
of your girlfriend, right?
Yes.
You can spend your life
here comfortably.
But you have decided.
Then fine.
Your girlfriend wants
you to struggle.
Get rejected everywhere.
Live the life of a common man.
Do what other common men do.
Then do it. Fine.
But Arjun, there is only one
problem in the life of honesty.
There is a lot of hard work..
..and the profit margin
is very little.
You explain to your girlfriend.
You are not my shooter that`s
murdering someone.
Match-fixing is happening
all around the world.
lt`s a business.
Players, boards, councils,
everyone is ready..
..then what`s the problem?
Arjun, if you don`t do this
work then someone else will.
But l want you to do this work.
And you know why?
Because you are good.
You are very good.
What are you thinking?
Remember Arjun what you had said?
Those who think will keep thinking.
So don`t think.
Fix the match.
And this heaven is yours.
Zoya, you are pregnant?
No. Queen Elizabeth is pregnant.
lt`s my name written on it, right?
Just a second.
Hello.
- Arjun.
Brother Shakeel, l told you
not to call here, right?
l wanted to ask you about the rate.
We will decide the rate
later, fine? - Fine.
Did you talk with Shahdab?
- Yes.
And you won`t call me, l will
call you, fine? - Fine. Ok.
Zoya!
Zoya, listen to me!
Zoya, you asked and l tried!
l put in my entire effort.
A small job or a business.
But l can`t do all this.
l am not made for all this.
l feel l should do
what l am good at.
Zoya, boss has given
a very big offer.
After that our life will
become king-size.
Zoya, it`s just a matter
of one match!
And l am doing all this for us.
For us! For us!
Not for us, oh God! For yourself!
l don`t want all this!
l don`t want this!
And this.. this is not
about one match, Arjun.
lt`s about your addiction! lt
is about habit! About sickness!
And you are sick!
You can never leave your habit of..
..betting, gambling and
match fixing, Arjun.
You are addicted.
And l`ve understood that today.
Zoya, listen to me. Listen to me.
Arjun, do you know
what my problem is?
l love you.. a lot.
l can`t see you dying.
l don`t have that courage, Arjun.
l am not that strong.
l can`t see you dying
in front of my eyes.
l`ll die! l`ll be killed! You`ve
developed this strange phobia.
Zoya, you have to use words
to fix a match and not guns!
Just get out of here!
Zoya! Zoya, listen to me.
Arjun, don`t make me weak anymore.
Just go, leave.
- Zoya!
Zoya!
Zoya! Listen to me. Open the door.
Zoya, whatever l am doing is right.
Zoya.
Why are you upset with me?
What mistake have l committed?
Why are you so far away from me?
Tell me what`s in your heart.
My darling l love you very much.
l am completely attracted
towards you.
Hi, have you seen Arjun today.
No, not at all.
Have you seen Arjun?
No.
Have you seen Arjun
today by any chance?
No, l haven`t seen him today.
Why isn`t Shahdab picking
up the phone?
Good, do one thing. Switch
off your phone too.
Listen Arjun, don`t
start all this again.
Let`s do one thing,
let`s refuse boss.
Refuse him? Are you mad?
Look Arjun, you are
about to be a father.
lf not for Zoya, then
do it for your child.
Let us go back to lndia.
lndia!
- Yes.
Back to the shanty where we spent
our childhood in poverty?
You want my child to
spend the same life?
You know Vishal, my parents
would never take me..
..from the route that
had a toy shop.
They were scared. What
if l liked something?
Shall l do the same
thing with my child?
Lie to him.
No.
Forget about asking, whatever
my child thinks about..
..he will get it.
Even today l haven`t forgotten
Zoya`s sorrowful face..
..when she was looking at that ring.
Today, she talks like
a crazy person.
l don`t want money, spend
the life of honesty.
But when she buys something
she likes..
..then there is a strange
happiness on her face.
The happiness of getting
what she wanted..
..the happiness to achieve it.
And l want to see the same
happiness on the face of my child.
And l am going to play
this last game..
Look Arjun you always
lose the last bet.
And you lose it so bad that..
And today even your queen
is not with you.
Where will she go?
l will appease her.
She loves me.
Vishal, come along if you want to..
..and don`t, if you don`t
want to, please.
He is still in his room.
He will come down in a while.
Here comes our player.
Checked lndia, have you?
We`ll go upstairs, check in..
..come back from downstairs.
We`ll have some lunch.
l`ll just come.
Sounds perfect.Jimmy.
- Yes.
Tell you what?lf you`ll be..
Ready?
- Yes ma`am.
Where is he going?l don`t know.
You will bat after winning the toss.
Okay.
- Your total will be 240.
ls the middle order set?
- Yes.
Okay, the fielding will be set too.
By Allah, everything is set.
Okay.-You have to give 200 runs
in the second innings.
Okay.
ls everything clear?
- Yes, everything is clear..
..Okay, have you received your money?
Jesus, what`s going
on here, Shahdab?
What the hell is this?
What are you doing here man?
Money, these guys.
What? Oh no, no.
Yes, you are taking money.
You are fixing the match,
aren`t you.
No, it`s not like that. -Look at
this. What the hell is going on?
No, no when l came inside..
when l came.. - Shut up.
No gun, no gun.
Brother Shakeel, you have
brought a gun along.
Please keep the gun down.
l will deal with him.
Arjun, you sit down. Sit down.
l will talk to him..
..Keep the gun away..
..Arjun, quiet.Leave my hand..
..Leave my hand.l will deal with
him! l will deal with him..
..Let me deal with him!
- Move.
Hey You!
Have you gone mad?Leave me,
l will deal with him.
O no!
Let`s go from here, come
on quickly, leave him.
What have you done?
l had told you-!Leave him now,
let`s get out from here!-No,
we can`t leave him,
do something.
You shut up!
- Quiet.
Come on, let us get out.
Arrest them.
Hands up!These guys.
l didn`t do anything!
- Quiet.
He shot him! Yes.
Arjun!
Let`s go.
Come on, come on!
Get the car!
Arjun!
Arjun stop!
No firing.
Yes, tell me.
Vishal, meet me at Sea Street!
- What?
Sea Street.
What are you saying, l
can`t hear.-Sea street.
- Where are you?
Attention all units,
nobody will fire.
l repeat! Nobody will fire!
There he is.
Arjun!
Stop running!
Arjun stop! Stop right there!
Don`t move Arjun!
Arjun, stop there!
Arjun!
Arjun, get in the car!
What happened to you?-Come on.
Come on, stop the car.
Let`s go.Let`s go.
What has happened to you?
Nothing, today l have
become colourful too.
You, never listen to me.
Just see now.-Nothing will happen.
lt`s just one bullet.
Whom are you calling?
- Zoya.
Hello Arjun. - Zoya, meet me right
now at City Centre mall.
Are you fine, Arjun?
Don`t ask questions,
do as l tell you.
But where..
ln a shocking turn of events
international cricket coach..
..Richard Nell has been found
dead in his hotel room.
lt is alleged that he
has been murdered.
Arjun Dixit, the high profile ..
match fixeris the prime suspect.
The police say he is on
the run as we speak.
Arjun, it`s bleeding a lot.
l will take you to the hospital.
No. My pain-reliever is my queen.
l will be fine once l meet her.
You know Vishal, if
l survive today..
..then l will marry her.
l have already lost her once.
l don`t want to lose her again.
Go!
Arjun.
Arjun, what did you do?
My fear turned out to be true.
Everything is done with words.
Did that coach die while conversing?
Arjun, did you kill that coach?
Zoya, l haven`t killed
the coach, believe me.
That Shakeel.. l didn`t know that..
Zoya, you weren`t with
me that`s why..
Now that you are with me,
everything will be fine.
Zoya, come on let`s
go away from here.
l have a lot of money. We
will start a new life.
From today, l will do what
you will tell me to. Okay?
Zoya, the police will
be arriving any minute.
Zoya, l don`t want to die, please.
You have killed the coach, isn`t it?
Zoya, l am not lying
this time, l swear.
l swear on you.
l swear on our child.
Zoya please. Let`s go
from here, please.
Arjun, then we won`t go from here.
We will stay here and face the law.
Zoya, you don`t know them,
they will kill me.
Zoya, l don`t want to die.
Arjun!
You trust me Arjun, isn`t it?
l am there with you.
Trust me Arjun.
Zoya, please let`s go.
Arjun, l am there.
l won`t let anything happen to you.
Trust me.
Arjun, come on.
Give yourself up, Arjun!
You love me, don`t you Arjun?
l won`t let anything happen to you.
Trust me.
Surrender yourself, please.
Arjun, do it.
Surrender yourself.
Arjun, don`t move!
Sir, he is ready to surrender!
Sir, please don`t shoot.
Sir, he has not committed
the murder.
Zoya, tell Arjun to surrender!
Arjun! Arjun, please surrender.
Arjun, drop the gun.
Arjun, drop the gun now.
This is your last chance Arjun!
Please don`t fire, sir,
he is ready to surrender.
Hold your fire!
Nobody will fire, nobody
will fire until l say so!
Arjun, this is your last chance.
Zoya, ask him to throw down his gun.
Tell him to surrender.
He doesn`t have any other option.
Arjun! Arjun, please.
Sir, he is going to surrender.
Please don`t shoot.
Arjun put the gun down. They
are going to shoot you..
..Oh God, don`t you get it!
Sir, don`t fire.
- Nobody will fire.
Hold positions.
Yes Arjun! Hold positions.
Sir, believe me. He is innocent.
Arjun didn`t do anything.
Sir, please. He has
surrendered, sir.
Sir, believe me.
Arjun!
Stop firing!
Stop firing, oh God!
Put the gun down.
Arjun!
You idiots!
You idiots, you killed him!
You lousy murderers!
Arjun!
You idiots, you go away from here.
Go!
Arjun! Nothing will happen to you.
Arjun, you will be fine.
Nothing will happen to you.
Nothing.
Arjun.
Arjun, l won`t let anything
happen to you.
Nothing.
Arjun!
Mama, come on please.-Yes son.
Mama, look this is so nice.
l want to play with it.
Okay, when we reach home you
can play with it, okay?
Okay.
2800!
Take this out, and this.
Now?
1800!
l am still short.
Do one thing, take that out too.
Mama.
- Yes son?
l don`t want this.
Give me some place in your heart.
Make me yours a bit.
Awaken me a bit in your dreams.
Hold me in your memories a bit.
My darling, l love you very much.
l`m helplessly attracted to you.
Now the destination isn`t too far.
There`s just a little
distance left.
Don`t go away leaving
me like this.
Without you every joy
is meaningless.
My darling, l love you very much.
l`m helplessly attracted to you.
Give me some place in your heart.
Make me yours a bit.
Awaken me a bit in your dreams.
Hold me in your memories a bit.